-当然能  -我会把合同发给你的  就这么定了
- Of course I can. - I'll send over a contract, iron-clad.
我不想再冒险让那混蛋跑路了
I don't want to risk that jerkwad skipping town again.
-在宣传前确保他先签字  -保证做到
- Make sure he signs it before the pitch. - Uh, will do.
振作点  孩子  马马虎虎不是你的风格
And, uh, go easy on the sauce, huh, kid? Sloppy don't suit you.
橡胶鸡  橡胶鸡
Rubber chicken Rubber chicken
这破旋律在我脑海里挥之不去了
Ah, I got that damn thing stuck in my head.
伙计们  那真是太棒了
Guys, that was amazing!
但是如果我们去
But if we're going to
说服尤兰达我们准备好去演出了
convince Yolanda we're ready for the big top,
我们真的得在接下来的一周好好休整一下
we need to really hunker down over the next week
排出绝对搞笑并且乐观向上
and put together a show so undeniably hilarious
热爱生命的表演  让她只能说
and life-affirming, that she has no choice but to say...